actively sharing stuff.
Do you wish you had more control over
that and it was less nebulous? I guess
like yeah I always wondered in in some
way that's like
why is there not more autonomy front? I
guess
it's one of those things that I do wish
there was more autonomy like I wish I
had more agency but at the same time I
know that if I were giving more agency
it would be overwhelming if you wanted
to have to pick every single thing you
see. It's so many decisions per day and
I already feel like I'm overwhelmed by
the number of real decisions I have to
make. So it's almost like as much as I
say I want this, I feel like a part of
me is okay with it being outsourced. One